Register of the Poland. Poselstwo (Portugal) Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- SERIES NO. 761d. COMMUNISTS
  - 1935
    - Circulars (Folder 38: 10)
  - 1939. (Folder 38: 11)
    List of documents
- SERIES NO. 761h. JEWISH MOVEMENT, 1935 (Folder 38: 12)
- SERIES NO. 763b. ARRESTS BY FOREIGN AUTHORITIES, 1939. (Folder 38: 13)
- SERIES NO. 764. INTERNAL POLITICAL SITUATION IN POLAND, 1937 (Folder 38: 14)
- SERIES NO. 773. ECONOMIC ISSUES. INFORMATION ON TRADE
  - 1935
    - General
      - General (Folder 38: 15)
      - Agricultural products (Folder 38: 16)
      - Caoutchouc (Box-folder 39: 1)
      - Chemical products (Folder 39: 2)
      - Gun powder (Folder 39: 3)
      - Iron products (Folder 39: 4)
      - Textiles (Folder 39: 5)
      - Wood (Folder 39: 6)
    - Firms - Sepewe (Folder 39: 7)
  - 1936
    - General
      - General (Folder 39: 8)
      - Agricultural products (Folder 39: 9)
      - Chemical products (Folder 39: 10)
      - Gun powder (Folder 39: 11)
      - Iron (Folder 39: 12)
      - Wood (Folder 39: 13)
    - Firms, including Sepewe (Folder 39: 14)
  - 1937
    - General (Folder 39: 15)
    - Agricultural products (Folder 39: 16)
    - Chemical products (Box-folder 40: 1)
    - Iron (Folder 40: 2)
    - Paper (Folder 40: 3)
    - Radios (Folder 40: 4)
    - Textiles (Folder 40: 5)
    - Wood (Folder 40: 6)
  - 1938
    - General (Folder 40: 7)
    - Agricultural products (Folder 40: 8)
    - Industrial products (Folder 40: 9)
    - Woods (Folder 40: 10)
  - 1939
    - General
      - Agricultural products (Folder 40: 11)
      - Chemical products (Folder 40: 12)
      - Iron (Folder 40: 13)
      - Radios (Folder 40: 14)
      - Textiles (Folder 40: 15)
      - Wood (Folder 40: 16)
    - Trade companies (Folder 40: 17)
  - 1940 (Folder 40: 18)
- SERIES NO. 774. COMPLAINTS ABOUT TRADE PRACTICES
  - 1936-1937 (Folder 40: 19)
  - 1939 (Folder 40: 20)
- SERIES NO. 777. INVENTIONS AND PATENTS, 1936 (Folder 40: 21)
- SERIES NO. 778. VALORIZATION AND CONVERSION
  - 1936 (Folder 40: 22)
  - 1939 (Folder 40: 23)
- SERIES NO. 779. STATE LOTTERY, 1937
  - General (Folder 40: 24)
  - Cegielski Ltd. (Folder 40: 25)
- SERIES NO. 784. PENSIONS AND OTHER SERVICES (Box 41)
  - 1934 (Folder 41: 1)
  - 1942 (Folder 41: 2)
- SERIES NO. 787. REPATRIATION
  - 1938 (Folder 41: 3)
  - 1939 (Folder 41: 4)
- SERIES NO. 788a. LOANS AND RELIEF PROVIDED TO POLISH CITIZENS
  - 1936 (Folder 41: 5)
  - 1939 (Folder 41: 6)
- SERIES NO. 788b. LOANS AND RELIEF PROVIDED TO CITIZENS OF GDANSK
  - 1935 (Folder 41: 7)
  - 1936 (Folder 41: 8)
  - 1937 (Folder 41: 9)
  - 1938 (Folder 41: 10)
  - 1939 (Folder 41: 11)
- SERIES NO. 789a. HEALTH CARE COSTS OF POLISH CITIZENS ABROAD, 1936 (Folder 41: 12)
- SERIES NO. 790. POLSKI CZERWONY KRZYZ (P0LISH RED CROSS)
  - 1939 (Folder 41: 13)
  - 1940 (Folder 41: 14)
  - 1942 (Folder 41: 15)
  - 1944 (Folder 41: 16)
- SERIES NO. 791. DONATIONS AND COLLECTIONS FOR VARIOUS CAUSES
  - 1939
    - General (Folder 41: 17)
    - Fundusz Obrony Narodowej (Folder 41: 18)
  - 1941 - Fundusz Obrony Narodowej (Folder 41: 19)
  - 1942 (Folder 41: 20)
  - 1945 (Folder 41: 21)
- SERIES NO. 792. COMMISSION FOR POLISH RELIEF, 1940 (Folder 41: 22)
- SERIES NO. 797a. MEDICAL PRACTICE OF POLISH DOCTORS ABROAD, 1936 (Folder 41: 23)
- SERIES NO. 801. INDIVIDUALS SEARCHED FOR AND PROCUREMENT OF ADDRESSES, 1938 (Folder 41: 24)
- SERIES NO. 802d. MAIL FORWARDING, 1936 (Folder 41: 25)
- SERIES NO. 806a. QUESTIONNAIRES AND INFORMATION ON COMMERCE AND INDUSTRY
  - 1936 (Folder 41: 26)
  - 1940 (Folder 41: 27)
- SERIES NO. 806c. QUESTIONNAIRES AND INFORMATION ON SCIENCE
  - 1936 (Folder 41: 28)
  - 1938 (Folder 41: 29)
- SERIES NO. 806g. QUESTIONNAIRES AND INFORMATION ON SHIP FARES, 1935 (Folder 41: 30)
- SERIES NO. 817. CONSTITUTION OF THE REPUBLIC OF POLAND, 1935 (Box-folder 42: 1)
- SERIES NO. 819. MINISTERSTWO SKARBU (MINISTRY OF TREASURY). FINANCIAL TRANSACTIONS, TRANSFERS, FUNDING OF SECRET AND OFFICIAL GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS DURING WARTIME, 1936-1940 (Folder 42: 2)
- SERIES. 821. DECREES AND RESOLUTIONS OF COUNCIL OF MINISTERS, 1942-1943 (Folder 42: 3)
- SERIES NO. 825. NACZELNY WODZ (SUPREME COMMANDER), 1938
  - "O exercito polaco e o seu chefe." (Folder 42: 4)
    Typescript
  - "L'armée polonaise et son chef." (Folder 42: 5)
- SERIES NO. 827. PROPAGANDA ON GOVERNMENT ACTIONS, 1940 (Folder 42: 6)
- SERIES NO. 829. POLISH GOVERNMENT-IN-EXILE, 1940
  - General (Folder 42: 7)
  - Government structure (Folder 42: 8)
- SERIES NO. 835. PANSTWOWY INSTYTUT EKSPORTOWY (STATE EXPORT INSTITUTE), 1934-1935 (Folder 42: 9)
- SERIES NO. 836. POSTAL AND TELEGRAPHIC SERVICES, 1940-1942 (Folder 42: 10)
- SERIES NO. 842. BANK POLSKI, 1937 (Folder 42: 11)
- SERIES NO. 851a. MINORITIES IN POLAND AND AFFAIRS RELATED TO THEM OUTSIDE OF POLAND - GERMANS
  - 1934 (Folder 42: 12)
  - 1939 (Folder 42: 13)
- SERIES NO. 851b. MINORITIES IN POLAND AND AFFAIRS RELATED TO THEM OUTSIDE OF POLAND - UKRAINIANS
  - 1936 (Folder 42: 14)
  - 1940-1943 (Folder 42: 15)
- SERIES NO. 851E. MINORITIES IN POLAND AND AFFAIRS RELATED TO THEM OUTSIDE OF POLAND - JEWS
  - 1935 (Folder 42: 16)
  - 1937-1938. (Folder 42: 17)
- SERIES NO. 880. HIGH COMMISSIONER OF THE LEAGUE OF NATIONS IN GDANSK, 1936 (Folder 42: 18)
- SERIES NO. 886. CONDUCT OF GDANSK FOREIGN AFFAIRS
  - 1933-1934 (Folder 42: 19)
  - 1936 (Folder 42: 20)
  - 1939 (Folder 42: 21)
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1931-1939 (Box 43)
  - 2 prints of Marshal Jozef Pilsudski's face after his death and plaster death mask (Folder 43: 1)
  - 3 prints of crowds gathered outside of Belweder, Marshal Jozef Pilsudski's residence, after his death (Folder 43: 2)
  - 2 prints of Jozef Pilsudski's funeral ceremony at Wawel Royal Castle in Krakow, Poland (Folder 43: 3)
  - 1 print of Marshall Jozef Pilsudski on SS Jadwiga Gdynia, n.d. (Folder 43: 4)
  - 16 prints of the mass celebrations and unveiling of the plaque outside of Marshal Pilsudski's residence on Madeira, Spain, 1935 (Folder 43: 5)
  - 1 print of Marshal Jozef Pilsudski on Madeira, 1934 (Folder 43: 6)
  - 9 prints of Queen Juliana's visit to Krakow and Krynica, Poland, n.d. (Folder 43: 7)
  - 6 prints depicting a commemorative mass for Marshal Jozef Pilsudzki, celebrated in Lisbon, Portugal, n.d. (Folder 43: 8)
  - 3 prints depicting a meeting of the Grupo Amizade Luso-Polaca, in Lisbon, Portugal, 1938 (Folder 43: 9)
  - 4 prints depicting the Gordon-Bennett Balloon competition in 1936 and the winners Zbigniew Burzynski and Wladyslaw Wysocki (Folder 43: 10)
  - 13 prints depicting Polish crews and planes participating in a Challenge aerial competition, 1934 (Folder 43: 11)
  - 8 prints depicting scenes related to "Pozyczka Narodowa" action in the late 1930s in Poland (Folder 43: 12)
  - 2 prints depicting Marian Chodacki, Poland's General Commissioner to Gdansk, n.d. (Folder 43: 13)
  - 1 print depicting Edward Raczkiewicz at the train station in Warsaw, 1930s (Folder 43: 14)
  - 1 print depicting the ceremony of accreditation of the Portuguese envoy to Poland at the Royal Castle, Warsaw, September 5, 1933 (Folder 43: 15)
- SCORES, n.d. (Folder 43: 16)
- ANNEX.